<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VCE_RawOnion.label>цибуля</VCE_RawOnion.label>
  <VCE_RawOnion.description>An edible bulb of pungent, savory taste and smell with almost as many varieties as cooking applications.</VCE_RawOnion.description>

  <VCE_RawPumpkin.label>гарбуз</VCE_RawPumpkin.label>
  <VCE_RawPumpkin.description>Technically a giant berry, pumpkins are renowned for being trivial to both sow and harvest.</VCE_RawPumpkin.description>

  <VCE_RawPepper.label>перець</VCE_RawPepper.label>
  <VCE_RawPepper.description>Tiny, spicy, crimson pods often used in sauces, relishes, or powders. While the flavor itself is mild the capsaicin contained inside means humans find them oddly addicting, if painful when consumed in mass. Animals are known to avoid eating the plant entirely.</VCE_RawPepper.description>

  <VCE_RawPeas.label>горох</VCE_RawPeas.label>
  <VCE_RawPeas.description>Spherical green seeds tucked safely away in a fleshy pod. Peas are notable for having potentially long shelf-lives when dried properly.</VCE_RawPeas.description>

  <VCE_RawEggplant.label>баклажани</VCE_RawEggplant.label>
  <VCE_RawEggplant.description>A bulbous purple fruit of the nightshade family. Eggplant is rarely served as a side, generally filling the role of the main component of the dish.</VCE_RawEggplant.description>

  <VCE_RawCabbage.label>капуста</VCE_RawCabbage.label>
  <VCE_RawCabbage.description>A somewhat hardy, leafy green vegetable, often chopped and then fermented or stewed.</VCE_RawCabbage.description>

  <VCE_RawBeets.label>буряк</VCE_RawBeets.label>
  <VCE_RawBeets.description>An herb-like vegetable widely cultivated for humans and livestock alike, notably nutritious and historically used in dye making.</VCE_RawBeets.description>

  <VCE_RawTomatoes.label>помідор</VCE_RawTomatoes.label>
  <VCE_RawTomatoes.description>A series of juicy, glossy red fruits attached by vine, used commonly as a vegetable. Strong stewing releases natural sugars and mellows out acids contained within.</VCE_RawTomatoes.description>


</LanguageData>