<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VCE_RawApple.label>яблуко</VCE_RawApple.label>
  <VCE_RawApple.description>Glossy, red apples. Apples have been used as snacking food, a dessert ingredient, and brewed into cider since early mankind.</VCE_RawApple.description>

  <VCE_RawPeach.label>персик</VCE_RawPeach.label>
  <VCE_RawPeach.description>An edible juicy fruit called peach or nectarine. A ripe peach will have a fragrant aroma and be delicious eaten fresh out of hand.</VCE_RawPeach.description>

  <VCE_RawCherry.label>вишня</VCE_RawCherry.label>
  <VCE_RawCherry.description>Tiny purple-red sweet cherries. Cherries are notable for requiring a brief freezing season, as such they quickly became a favorite among northern occidental cultures.</VCE_RawCherry.description>

  <VCE_RawPlum.label>слива</VCE_RawPlum.label>
  <VCE_RawPlum.description>A smooth-skinned purple fruit. Many cultures dry-age plums into prunes for long-term preservation. Instead of rotting, once the 15 days have passed the plums will dry into prunes, which are considered preserved food.</VCE_RawPlum.description>

  <VCE_RawPrunes.label>чорнослив</VCE_RawPrunes.label>
  <VCE_RawPrunes.description>Dried plums. Prunes take a very long time to deteriorate.</VCE_RawPrunes.description>

  <VCE_RawPear.label>груша</VCE_RawPear.label>
  <VCE_RawPear.description>Crispy green pears. While at first similar to apples, pears are slightly more fibrous and less sweet.</VCE_RawPear.description>

  <VCE_RawPricklyPear.label>опунція</VCE_RawPricklyPear.label>
  <VCE_RawPricklyPear.description>Pink, melon-like edible fruits, used historically for both snacking as well as medicine by desert natives.</VCE_RawPricklyPear.description>

  <VCE_Bearberry.label>барбарис</VCE_Bearberry.label>
  <VCE_Bearberry.description>These are small, pink berries known as bearberries. While raw bearberries possess an acidic and bland taste, after cooking a natural sweetness comes through and the results can be much more palatable.</VCE_Bearberry.description>

  <VCE_RawBanana.label>банан</VCE_RawBanana.label>
  <VCE_RawBanana.description>Yellow, elongated berries, easily peeled to reveal a deeply sweet, nearly mushy flesh inside. They have been a favorite of both humans and other primates across the tropics for millenia.</VCE_RawBanana.description>

  <VCE_RawOrange.label>апельсин</VCE_RawOrange.label>
  <VCE_RawOrange.description>Spherical and perforated, oranges are notoriously annoying to peel and quite pulpy, but known as one of the absolute juiciest fruits with a bright tang and sour aftertaste.</VCE_RawOrange.description>

</LanguageData>