<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VCE_RawCelery.label>селера</VCE_RawCelery.label>
  <VCE_RawCelery.description>A vegetable consisting of a long fibrous stalk tapering into leaves. The leaves are strongly flavored and are used less often, either as a flavoring in soups and stews or as a dried herb. Celery is a staple in many soups.</VCE_RawCelery.description>

  <VCE_RawLettuce.label>салатна капуста</VCE_RawLettuce.label>
  <VCE_RawLettuce.description>A leaf vegetable commonly eaten fresh and served as the base of green salads. Lettuce is generally a rich source of vitamins K and A.</VCE_RawLettuce.description>

  <VCE_RawRadish.label>редис</VCE_RawRadish.label>
  <VCE_RawRadish.description>An edible root vegetable that is very easy to grow and quick to harvest. Radishes are often planted by novice gardeners.</VCE_RawRadish.description>

  <VCE_RawBuckwheat.label>гречка</VCE_RawBuckwheat.label>
  <VCE_RawBuckwheat.description>A pseudocereal cultivated for its grain-like seeds. Its white flowers are produced in terminal clusters and after pòllination turn into triangular-shaped seeds that are enclosed by a tough dark brown or gray rind.</VCE_RawBuckwheat.description>

  <VCE_RawPeanut.label>арахіс</VCE_RawPeanut.label>
  <VCE_RawPeanut.description>Seeds with an oblong shape and a papery seed coat. Similar in taste and nutritional profile to tree nuts such as walnuts and almonds, but technically a legume.</VCE_RawPeanut.description>

  <VCE_RawSunflower.label>соняшник</VCE_RawSunflower.label>
  <VCE_RawSunflower.description>The seeds of the sunflower plant are more commonly eaten as a snack than as part of a meal. They can also be used as garnishes or ingredients in various recipes.</VCE_RawSunflower.description>

  <VCE_RawOkra.label>бамія</VCE_RawOkra.label>
  <VCE_RawOkra.description>Edible green seed pods, famously known for their slimy or sticky texture when cut open. Okra is a powerhouse of valuable nutrients.</VCE_RawOkra.description>

  <VCE_RawGarlic.label>часник</VCE_RawGarlic.label>
  <VCE_RawGarlic.description>A very old crop which is cultivated for its bulb, formed in the base of the leaves. It is highly appreciated in cooking for its pungent and characteristic taste.</VCE_RawGarlic.description>

  <VCE_RawCarrot.label>морква</VCE_RawCarrot.label>
  <VCE_RawCarrot.description>A root vegetable, typically orange in color, though purple, black, red, white, and yellow cultivars exist. A versatile food that can be chopped and boiled, fried or steamed, cooked in soups and stews, as well as used for baby and pet foods.</VCE_RawCarrot.description>

  <VCE_RawBrusselsSprouts.label>брюссельська капуста</VCE_RawBrusselsSprouts.label>
  <VCE_RawBrusselsSprouts.description>A form of cabbage grown for its edible buds called "sprouts". Brussels sprouts usually are eaten cooked, and the small young sprouts have a more delicate flavour than older ones.</VCE_RawBrusselsSprouts.description>

  <VCE_RawOlives.label>маслини</VCE_RawOlives.label>
  <VCE_RawOlives.description>A small, egg-shaped black or green fruit that is used as food or for making oil. Olives freshly picked from the tree contain oleuropein, which makes the fruit unpalatable for immediate consumption. They must be brined or fermented to be used.</VCE_RawOlives.description>

  <VCE_RawSweetPotatoes.label>солодка картопля</VCE_RawSweetPotatoes.label>
  <VCE_RawSweetPotatoes.description>Large, starchy, sweet-tasting (tasting similar to pumpkin), tuberous roots that are used as a root vegetable. The sweet potato is distantly related to the common potato.</VCE_RawSweetPotatoes.description>

  <VCE_RawCassava.label>маніок</VCE_RawCassava.label>
  <VCE_RawCassava.description>A tuberous edible plant also called manioc, mandioca, or yuca. They have a mild nutty taste and are commonly eaten as root vegetables in stews or as side dishes. Cassava roots are a versatile vegetable that can be used to produce flour, breads, tapioca, a laundry starch, and an alcoholic beverage.</VCE_RawCassava.description>

  <VCE_RawBeans.label>стручкова квасоля</VCE_RawBeans.label>
  <VCE_RawBeans.description>Young, unripe fruits of a cultivar of the common bean. They can be steamed, boiled, stir-fried, or baked. They are commonly cooked in other dishes such as soups, stews, and casseroles. Green beans can also be pickled, much like cucumbers are.</VCE_RawBeans.description>

  <VCE_RawBellPeppers.label>червоний болгарський перець</VCE_RawBellPeppers.label>
  <VCE_RawBellPeppers.description>Also known as sweet peppers, bell peppers are technically nightshades and part of the capsicum family, but they are the only chili pepper that carries a recessive gene that stops any capsaicin from being made in the fruit, thus making them not spicy.</VCE_RawBellPeppers.description>

  <VCE_RawYellowBellPeppers.label>жовтий болгарський перець</VCE_RawYellowBellPeppers.label>
  <VCE_RawYellowBellPeppers.description>Also known as sweet peppers, bell peppers are technically nightshades and part of the capsicum family, but they are the only chili pepper that carries a recessive gene that stops any capsaicin from being made in the fruit, thus making them not spicy.</VCE_RawYellowBellPeppers.description>

  <VCE_RawChickpeas.label>нут</VCE_RawChickpeas.label>
  <VCE_RawChickpeas.description>One of the earliest cultivated legumes. Chickpeas are high in fibre and protein and are a good source of iron, phosphorus, and folic acid.</VCE_RawChickpeas.description>

  <VCE_RawTaro.label>коріння таро</VCE_RawTaro.label>
  <VCE_RawTaro.description>A starchy root vegetable. It has a brown outer skin and white flesh with purple specks throughout. When cooked, it has a mildly sweet taste and a texture similar to potato.</VCE_RawTaro.description>

  <VCE_RawWatercress.label>настурція</VCE_RawWatercress.label>
  <VCE_RawWatercress.description>A green leaf vegetable rich in vitamins and minerals and from the same family as kale and broccoli.</VCE_RawWatercress.description>

  <VCE_RawLotus.label>лотус</VCE_RawLotus.label>
  <VCE_RawLotus.description>The seeds of the lotus plant. They are packed with nutritional elements which make them an excellent choice for a healthy diet, with a high content of proteins, carbohydrates, and vitamins.</VCE_RawLotus.description>

  <VCE_RawWaterChestnut.label>водяний горіх</VCE_RawWaterChestnut.label>
  <VCE_RawWaterChestnut.description>Small, rounded corms with a crisp, white flesh that may be eaten raw, slightly boiled, or grilled.</VCE_RawWaterChestnut.description>

  <VCE_RawCucumber.label>огірок</VCE_RawCucumber.label>
  <VCE_RawCucumber.description>A long thin vegetable with hard green skin and wet transparent flesh. Can be eaten raw.</VCE_RawCucumber.description>

  <VCE_RawButternutSquash.label>бутернатовий гарбуз</VCE_RawButternutSquash.label>
  <VCE_RawButternutSquash.description>A vegetable with a sweet, nutty taste similar to that of a pumpkin. It has tan-yellow skin and orange fleshy pulp with a compartment of seeds in the blossom end.</VCE_RawButternutSquash.description>


</LanguageData>